const questions = [
  {
    question: 'Which one is the smallest ocean in world ?',
    options: { a: 'Indian', b: 'pacific', c: 'Atlantic', d: 'Arctic' },
    answer: 'Arctic',
    reward : 1000
  },
  {
    question: 'Dead sea is located between which two countries ?',
    options: { a: 'Jordan and Sudan', b: 'Jordan and Israel', c: 'Turkey and UAE', d: 'UAE and Egypt' },
    answer: 'Jordan and Israel',
    reward : 2000
  },
  {
    question: 'In which country, white elephant is found',
    options: { a:'India', b:'Sri Lanka', c:'Thailand', d:'Malaysia'},
    answer: 'Thailand',
    reward : 3000
  },
  {
    question: 'Total number of oceans in the world is',
    options: { a:3, b:7, c:5, d:12},
    answer: 5,
    reward : 4000
  },
  {
    question: 'Which one is the biggest iceland in the world ?',
    options: { a:'Greenland', b:'Finland', c:'Sumatra', d:'Borneo'},
    answer: 'Greenland',
    reward : 5000
  },
  {
    question: 'Joule is the unit of',
    options: { a:'temperature', b:'pressure', c:'energy', d:'heat'},
    answer: 'energy',
    reward : 4500
  },
  {
    question: 'Which airport is set to be renamed as Maryada Purushottam Sriram Airport?',
    options: { a:'Varanasi', b:'Haridwar', c:'Ayodhya', d:'Lucknow'},
    answer: 'Ayodhya',
    reward : 10000
  },
  {
    question: 'Maximum number of seats in the Rajya Sabha is in',
    options: { a:'Bihar', b:'Uttar Pradesh', c:'Andhra Pradesh', d:'West Bengal'},
    answer: 'Uttar Pradesh',
    reward : 5500
  },
  {
    question: 'Who was Indiaâ€™s first President ?',
    options: { a:'Radha Krishnan', b:'Zakir Hussain', c:'V. V. Giri', d:'Rajendra Prasad'},
    answer: 'Rajendra Prasad',
    reward : 9000
  },
  {
    question: 'Where is the Election Commission located ?',
    options: { a:'Chennai', b:'New Delhi', c:'Mumbai', d:'Kolkata'},
    answer: 'New Delhi',
    reward : 8000
  }
];

exports.questions = questions;